They say seven out of ten high school
couples break up within a year.
If you include after graduation,
almost all of them are destined to break up.
Even so, people still get swept up in love.
In the tears. In the laughter.
I don't have a lot of confidence,
in reality or in myself,
that I'll ever find my world changed
by a fleeting relationship like that.
But sometimes, I wonder.
What if I actually did have an
experience like that in my teens?
What if I did find a teary-eyed
heroine standing before me?
What if I was the main
character in a light novel?
If that happened...
what would I think about it?
You did your best, big brother!
I know it must've been hard.
"I know all about how dedicated you are."
"So if you need anyone to lean on,
your little Kurumi is right here for you."
Oh, this is so good.
And I'm finally about to get to the climax!
Every book in this series has twenty pages
of the lead getting totally pampered.
You can't, Sosuke!
You can't be wasting time like this!
But...
They're in my class.
That's Yanami Anna and Hakamada Sosuke.
Why are they having a lovers'
quarrel in a place like this?
If you don't go see her now,
Karen-chan is gonna leave for England!
Don't you care about that?
Karen must be that girl
who transferred recently.
A-ha! You're that molester from before!
She's already transferring again?
And to England?
The story's moving way too fast!
But Karen... already said goodbye to me.
That obviously means she
wants you to go see her!
How would you know—
Because I get it!
I mean, that's how I've always
felt about you, Sosuke.
Anna...
I...
Go to her. Karen-chan's waiting for you.
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize to me, idiot.
Maybe I'll just pretend
I didn't see anything.
N-No! Anything but that!
Stop! That's so painfully desperate!
Miss! Are you all right?
I didn't see a thing.
Sosuke and I have been friends
since we were little.
Uh...
He made me a ring out of white clover.
He said he'd make me his wife.
His wife.
His wife... His wife!
Yanami-san, are you okay?!
For now, just drink that
and try to calm down.
Thanks. You're in my class...
Nukumizu-kun, right?
Huh? You're asking me that now?
This is really good.
It's rosehip tea.
It's supposed to be good for the skin.
For my skin?
I don't have anyone to show it off to.
Stop! Too graphic for me!
Extra large fries. Here you are.
Yes, thank you!
What? I didn't order that.
You're fine with honey mustard
and cod roe mayo for sauces, right?
Did you order that, Yanami-san?
Karen-chan's a dear friend of mine. But...
But you know, she just
transferred here in May!
Don't the twelve years I've known
Sosuke count for anything?
I'll ask one more time.
Was it you who ordered the fries?
Sosuke said he'd make me his wife.
Isn't that mean? What a liar, right?
When exactly did he say that?
It was before elementary school,
so we must've been about four or five.
Yeah, that doesn't count.
Wait. Does this mean he's cheating on me?
Were you and Hakamada actually dating?
Oh, gosh. I guess it probably looked that way.
So you weren't even going out?
Then it's not cheating at all!
I-I mean, it was basically like
we were half-dating, though.
And if that soggy cow hadn't waltzed onto
the scene, we'd probably still be together!
Wasn't she a "dear friend" a moment ago?
But I get it.
If I'd worked up the courage sooner,
things might not have turned out like this.
W-Well, you might be right.
I'm sorry I'm such a mess today.
No, it's totally fine.
That's not what you need to apologize for.
But I'm okay with it.
As long as Sosuke's happy, I'm okay with it.
What a spectacular reaction
to getting rejected.
Speaking of, there's a term that
perfectly describes girls like her.
Yanami Anna. Yes, it fits you perfectly.
You're a "losing heroine."
Too
Many
Losing
Heroines
Bicycle Parking Registration
Tsuwabuki High School
Few realize that the flavor of water
changes depending on the faucet.
I am one of those who does.
In the morning, the water from
this faucet really is the best.
It's the farthest one from
the water tank on the roof,
so the water has a much
lower chlorine content.
Once I've had my fill, I calculate the distance
and time it'll take me to get back to class.
If I get back too soon, I may find someone
in my seat, and that'd be annoying.
Perfect.
But someone's in my seat.
Ah, shoot. I guess that explains it.
4th Period: World History
will start 10 minutes late.
Independent study
until then!!
Huh. Looks like the archery team made it
to nationals for the third year in a row.
Okay, then the three of us
should eat lunch together!
Impressive.
I'm gonna pass on that.
Sosuke, be sure to take
good care of Karen-chan.
Anna!
You really are my best friend, Anna.
Even though she calls you a "soggy cow"?
Well, maybe Yanami's over it by now...
Wow. Yeah, she's not over anything yet.
Hey, Yanami-san.
U-Um, you're on duty today, right?
Amanatsu-sensei's asking for you
to go help in the printing room.
Oh, really? I'm on my way.
Nukumizu-kun, did you
say that to help me out?
Well, kind of.
Thanks.
Another second and I'd have had
a death grip on Karen-chan's boobs.
How can she say that with a straight face?
Oh, by the way, remember
how I paid for you on Friday?
Oh, yeah. Thanks for that.
I don't have my wallet on me, but maybe you
can meet me at the emergency stairs at lunch?
Huh?
The fire escape staircase.
In the old building.
Sure. As long as you pay me back.
You know, they actually started dating.
So why did they ask me to
eat with them? It's so weird.
And here I thought we were good friends.
I wonder if they're trying
to hurt me even more.
Are you guys seriously best friends?
Hey! Yanami!
What are you doing? Class is about to st—
Amana-chan, are you okay?
Ow, ow, ow. Thanks.
Amanatsu-sensei, aren't these
the wrong lesson materials?
Hey, I don't know who you think you are,
but get it together, man!
In second year, we cover the
Byzantine Empire! Viva Byzantine!
Sensei, your next class is 1-C.
Huh?!
And I'm actually one
of your students, Sensei.
Byzantine!
Not Byzantine.
Isn't that wild?
Please save me.
Karen-chan wants the three of us to
go do karaoke together after school.
So why don't you?
They're gonna make me
listen to them sing a duet!
Nukumizu-kun, are you
saying you want me to die?
Well, no... Uh, good luck, I guess.
So about the money from before—
That night...
I even got a message from Sosuke's sister.
"I can't get a hold of Sosuke.
Are you two together?"
Now, why in the world didn't
he see her messages? I wonder.
Somebody save me.
I wonder.
I wonder!
Sorry.
I can't talk about this with any
of my friends or acquaintances.
Guess that means I'm not
even an acquaintance.
So... do you think you can
finally pay me back now?
Here's the receipt from before.
Yeah, thanks so much for that.
You really saved my—
Oh, my. Did the total go up?
Yanami-san, you also got an order
of watermelon pancakes, remember?
Uh-huh.
And you finished up with
a pork shabu udon salad.
'Cause salads don't make you gain weight.
I'm not opposed to your faith
in salads. Not at all.
It's just an idea, but what if I were
to repay you in some other way?
Some other way?
I'm not actually very good at it,
so I'm not sure if it'll satisfy you,
but Sosuke used to say he really liked it.
Huh? What?!
She can't possibly mean
doing something wet and sticky!
No way! This is bad! And we're at school!
I...
Listen—
I'm not very good at cooking,
but I think I could manage a bento lunch!
A bento lunch?
Something wrong?
Oh, right! A bento lunch!
But one bento lunch
probably won't cover it...
Right, so I'll make you one every day
until it equals the amount on the receipt.
Uh, I'm not sure—
Okay, we'll start tomorrow.
I'll be waiting here.
Sure.
Receipt
Menu
Drinks Bar
Extra Large French Fries
Steak Meal
Hamburg Steak Meal
Salad
Soup
Watermelon Pancake
Total
Looking forward to it.
U-Um, you're N-Nukumizu-kun, right?
I-I-I'm, um, a first-year
in the literature club—
Huh? Who? From where?
Um, my name is Komari.
From the literature club. Komari Chika.
U-Um, I need to speak with you!
A-About the club.
With me? What does the
literature club want with me?
W-Well, that's...
Nukumizu-kun, you're in the lit club, right?
Huh?
Come to think of it...
Just after I started here, I think I got talked
into signing up for the literature club.
"The student council sent out a warning about
members who aren't participating in the club"?
Nukumizu-kun, right? It's been a while.
I apologize. I think I've
been ghosting for a while.
It helps a lot having you back, though.
I'm the vice president, Tsukinoki Koto.
Third-year. Remember me?
Oh, sure. Of course I do.
Of course I'm lying.
Not a bad selection.
You can borrow whatever you want.
Just don't touch the Dazai or Mishima.
The student council has had
their eyes on us recently.
You are
the pen!!
You're gonna have to hang out
with us for a while. Okay, later.
Absolutely do not touch
the Dazai or Mishima, okay?
The BL genre aside, at least there's a
bunch of popular series I haven't read yet.
I don't need to worry about
lunch money for a while.
Maybe I can hold off on new books and catch
up on a few series the lit club doesn't have.
New Paperback
Reissue Lineup
You definitely have to buy
You're the Innocent Queen of Darkness.
At least up to volume 5, when my favorite
character starts turning to the dark side—
Kaju.
Why are you in my room?
I'm in here most of the time.
You just don't notice me.
What a creepy thing to say.
So, big brother, have you
made any friends at school?
Have no fear, big brother. I, Kaju,
will find you some friends without fail.
First of all, I'll make you a chara-ben.
Kmff-rhf-bmf?
Yes! A character bento's a great
conversation starter that'll win people over!
Oh, uh, I've actually got someone
making lunch for me for a while.
B-B-Big brother, are you saying
you're going out with a woman?!
No, I'm not!
Oh, of course not!
How could someone with
no friends have a girlfriend?
But isn't it strange to have a non-friend
non-girlfriend making lunch for you?
Well, I've actually paid for it.
Oh, eating out with a working girl?
It must be one of those "bento lunch" things.
My friends told me all about that.
Kaju.
Yes, what?
You need to find better friends.
Isn't that mean?
What is?
I'm talking about you!
I asked for your help yesterday.
I had to listen to the brand-new
couple singing duets together.
Can you imagine how that felt?!
So what about my lunch?
Here you go.
Um, what's this?
I tried to make two bento
lunches this morning,
and my mom was like,
"I'm sure Sosuke-kun will be thrilled!"
This is convenience store food, right?
That's why I couldn't make enough for two.
The packaging's clearly
handmade, but still...
Okay. Let's say this is 268 yen.
Too cheap!
But that's the actual price.
Fine. 300 yen.
Anyway, why don't you keep
your distance from those two?
Everyone's walking on eggshells
around me in class.
'Cause, like, Sosuke and I used
to be together all the time.
"Oh, what? Did Yanami get dumped?"
That's the vibe right now.
Um, I'm not sure what to...
Okay, 350 yen.
Balance
I heard you joined the lit club, Nukumizu.
My teacher told me they have
the complete works of Abe Kobo.
Can I borrow them sometime?
Oh, uh, that's probably okay.
I'll check with my senpai.
Thanks.
Mitsuki!
I'm skipping my club today.
Wanna go get something to eat?
Sorry. I have prep school today.
Huh? You're still a first-year.
If all you do is study,
you're just gonna get dumber.
And if you don't study more,
you'll end up repeating the year.
Mitsuki-san. We're going to be late
to cram school if we don't get going.
Oh, Chihaya. I'm coming.
See you later, Lemon.
Huh? Oh... Bye-bye.
Hey, are you and Mitsuki friends?
Uh, we're not exactly friends,
but we go to the same cram school—
So do you know who that girl was?
Um, Asagumo-san, I think?
She and Ayano are both
taking the advanced course.
Advanced course, huh?
I guess Mitsuki's into smart girls after all.
Lemon-chan, what are your intentions?
Huh? N-Nothing.
It's just, we've been in the same
class since elementary school...
Sounds like you're childhood friends.
Which means...
That woman is the homewrecker.
Oh, come on. "Homewrecker"?
Listen, Nukumizu-kun,
there are only two types of girls.
The childhood friend and the homewrecker.
I see.
But what a contrast!
Hey, what do those two look like to you?
They seem pretty friendly,
but didn't they meet just recently?
Maybe they're just plain friends.
Right! I'm sure they're just plain friends!
I knew you'd get it, Yana-chan!
Lemon-chan, I kinda feel like
we're not that different after all.
I'm rooting for you!
They're asking me to hang out again today.
"Wanna come study at Karen-chan's house?"
You should say no.
But if I don't go,
it'll be just the two of them!
That may be true, but where's my lunch?
Nukumizu-kun, you ever think this
might be why you don't have friends?
I don't need that from you.
Hold the lid a minute.
I only have one lunch box I can use,
so I shoved the two servings into one box.
Okay, let's eat.
Nukumizu-kun, how much is that worth?
Um, let's say 400 yen.
Nice! Not bad at all.
At this rate, I should be able to
pay it off by summer vacation.
Balance
yen
Sandwich, Karaage
Rice
Remaining
You can see the field from here.
Oh. Yeah.
Isn't that Lemon-chan over there?
Lemon-chan... She sure is fast.
I heard she placed in the
prefectural competition.
How'd you know that?
I'm no slouch when it comes to
reading the announcement board.
Lemon-chan's so cool.
I guess I really got dumped.
I understood it in my head, but I don't
think my body had figured it out yet.
I was here thinking,
"Wow, Lemon-chan sure can run."
And then it turned into
"Wow, I sure got dumped."
Nukumizu-kun, maybe if you get dumped flat
on your face someday, you'll know what I mean.
You think so?
Still, nothing changes after you've been dumped.
Doesn't even feel like a fresh start.
But still, everything around
you keeps moving on,
so you've got to keep moving, too.
I've never been dumped before,
so I don't really get it.
Spoken like a lady-killer.
They say seven out of ten high school
couples break up within a year.
If you include after graduation,
almost all of them are destined to break up.
Even so, people still get swept up in love.
In the tears. In the laughter.
I don't have a lot of confidence,
in reality or in myself,
that I'll ever find my world changed
by a fleeting relationship like that.
But sometimes, I wonder.
What if I actually did have an
experience like that in my teens?
What if I did find a teary-eyed
heroine standing before me?
What if I was the main
character in a light novel?
If that happened...
Episode 1
Professional Childhood Friend Yanami Anna's
Style of Losing
what would I think about it?